<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<!--
  ~ Copyright (c) 2021 Piruin P.
  -->
<odoo noupdate="1">
    <record id="category_social_history" model="ni.observation.category">
        <field name="code">social-history</field>
        <field name="name">Social History</field>
        <field name="definition">
            Social History Observations define the patient's occupational, personal (e.g.,
            lifestyle), social, familial, and environmental history and health risk factors that may impact the
            patient's health.
        </field>
    </record>
    <record id="category_vital_signs" model="ni.observation.category">
        <field name="code">vital-signs</field>
        <field name="name">Vital Signs</field>
        <field name="definition">
            Clinical observations measure the body's basic functions such as blood pressure, heart
            rate, respiratory rate, height, weight, body mass index, head circumference, pulse oximetry, temperature,
            and body surface area.
        </field>
    </record>
    <record id="category_imaging" model="ni.observation.category">
        <field name="code">imaging</field>
        <field name="name">Imaging</field>
        <field name="definition">
            Observations generated by imaging. The scope includes observations regarding plain
            x-ray, ultrasound, CT, MRI, angiography, echocardiography, and nuclear medicine.
        </field>
    </record>
    <record id="category_laboratory" model="ni.observation.category">
        <field name="code">laboratory</field>
        <field name="name">Laboratory</field>
        <field name="definition">
            The results of observations generated by laboratories. Laboratory results are typically
            generated by laboratories providing analytic services in areas such as chemistry, hematology, serology,
            histology, cytology, anatomic pathology (including digital pathology), microbiology, and/or virology. These
            observations are based on analysis of specimens obtained from the patient and submitted to the
            laboratory.
        </field>
    </record>
    <record id="category_procedure" model="ni.observation.category">
        <field name="code">procedure</field>
        <field name="name">Procedure</field>
        <field name="definition">
            Observations generated by other procedures. This category includes observations
            resulting from interventional and non-interventional procedures excluding laboratory and imaging (e.g.,
            cardiology catheterization, endoscopy, electrodiagnostics, etc.). Procedure results are typically generated
            by a clinician to provide more granular information about component observations made during a procedure. An
            example would be when a gastroenterologist reports the size of a polyp observed during a
            colonoscopy.
        </field>
    </record>
    <record id="category_survey" model="ni.observation.category">
        <field name="code">survey</field>
        <field name="name">Survey</field>
        <field name="definition">
            Assessment tool/survey instrument observations (e.g., Apgar Scores, Montreal Cognitive
            Assessment (MoCA)).
        </field>
    </record>
    <record id="category_exam" model="ni.observation.category">
        <field name="code">exam</field>
        <field name="name">Exam</field>
        <field name="definition">
            Observations generated by physical exam findings including direct observations made by
            a clinician and use of simple instruments and the result of simple maneuvers performed directly on the
            patient's body.
        </field>
    </record>
    <record id="category_therapy" model="ni.observation.category">
        <field name="code">therapy</field>
        <field name="name">Therapy</field>
        <field name="definition">
            Observations generated by non-interventional treatment protocols (e.g. occupational,
            physical, radiation, nutritional and medication therapy)
        </field>
    </record>
    <record id="category_activity" model="ni.observation.category">
        <field name="code">activity</field>
        <field name="name">Activity</field>
        <field name="definition">
            Observations that measure or record any bodily activity that enhances or maintains
            physical fitness and overall health and wellness. Not under direct supervision of practitioner such as a
            physical therapist. (e.g., laps swum, steps, sleep data)
        </field>
    </record>
</odoo>
